Guide to the School of Forestry, Yale University, Records of Training Camps
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Forestry, Yale University, records of training camps
1901-1962
RU 43
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(3 boxes)
The records consist of clippings, records, scrapbooks, and photographs which document the students and operations of the Yale School of Forestry's (called the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies after 1972) training camps.
Yale University. School of Forestry
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 24-E (YRG 24-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Forestry.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1982.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by material type and subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of clippings, records, scrapbooks, and photographs which document the students and operations of the Yale School of Forestry's (called the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies after 1972) training camps.
Conservation of natural resources; Environmental protection; Forest conservation; Forest management; Human ecology -- Study and teaching; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Forestry
- Records, Accession 1982-A-012
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Cook's Ledger, Milford Camp, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cook's Account Book, Milford Camp [Summer], 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Log, Milford Summer Camp, 1910-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Log, Summer Camp (Connecticut), 1927-1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leaves from Scrapbook with Photographs, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Newspaper clippings & map; Crossett, Ark, camp, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Camp Log; Crossett, Ark., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Outline for a Field Study of a Lumber Operation," Bryant, R.C., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Register, Milford Camp [Summer School], 1901-1909 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Newspapers Clippings[Scrapbook] Crossett, Arkansas Camp, 1946-1959 (Box 3)